<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tennis Player. Cricket Watcher. Thing Maker on Usman Khalid</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tennis Player. Cricket Watcher. Thing Maker on Usman Khalid</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating content aware asset renditions for AEM using Asset Compute Service &amp; Azure Cognitive Services</title>
      <link>/posts/aem-content-aware-renditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/aem-content-aware-renditions/</guid>
      <description>Asset renditions are an important piece of the DAM in Adobe Experience Manager. Out of the box, AEM creates a few renditions for each asset that is uploaded. These can be used for different viewports and devices or as thumbnails. However, what if we wanted to create a blurred or grayscale rendition for an asset? These are some simple use cases, but with Adobe’s asset compute service, we can extend the out of the box functionality to handle them and go even further to implement more complex scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>As far back as I can remember, I&amp;rsquo;ve always been interested in creating experiences on the web. When I was in high school, I took a media communications class and decided to make a website for an assignment. I loved the idea of creating something that people could see, interact with and use online. I remember using Adobe Dreamweaver and using layers to visually drag and drop elements on a page (not knowing that this was positioning everything absolutely) and it would break outside of that specific screen size.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
